[Music]
welcome to business Central lunch event
2025 release V
1 in this session I will show you new
set of powerbi reports related to
sustainability this is something what is
coming as a new uh in this session I
will show you reports but sustainability
app is coming with
26.1 so what is included here we have
set of reports first set of reports is
related to greenhouse gas emissions so
you can find realized emissions versus
Target and versus Baseline you can find
emissions by category and scope carbon
equivalent analyzis journey to Net Zero
carbon so many different uh powerbi
reports plus we have water and waste
analyzis because with this wave
introduce water and waste analyzis and
one more thing social analyzis even if
this is not related directly with
sustainability but this is related to
USG reporting so this part is related to
social governance so we enable one
report related to Social analyzis and on
the top of that we have sustainability
and
overview so let's turn to
demo okay let's look in new Barbi set of
reports and I will start with
sustainability over youw first you can
find some kpis realized for all three
gases and water and waste so this is
realized and then you can find carbon
equivalent different analyzis carbon
equivalent per uh category carbon
equivalent emission by mon carbon
equivalent emission by scope carbon
equivalent emission versus basine and
then plus water and base intensity water
and vase intensity by type so you have
the most important information on your
ability over you and then we can turn to
realized emissions versus Target and
again on the top you can find the most
important kpis first for carbon
equivalent and carbon so this is
realized versus Target your
sustainability goals and the same apply
for two other gases so you can control
completely uh this uh kpis versus
targets and plus you can see what is
your change in this period what is your
target again you have equivalent by
scope gas emission by categories so all
these details for all different gases
very similar realized versus this time
versus Baseline so not this is not
versus Target now this is versus
Baseline again equivalent carbon methan
nitrium oxide and uh again emission by
scope emission by Baseline now we can
switch to water and waste
analyzis here you can see water
intensity by different
countries we have here for example in
United States that we have 14,000 of uh
liters or met Cube depends uh how you uh
measure we have something in Australia
little bit more so you have all these
details about your water impact around
the world or in your country when you're
working or operating then if you uh
watched about um water and waste
management you maybe you already noticed
that we have responsibility Center as
facility uh uh operation so you can
track your uh water intensity against
your facility capacities then again you
have water change year over year um wte
change year over
year uh again water and vas intensity by
facility
water and vas intensity by type all
these details here so we can continue
emission by category so you have for all
categories all emissions we can track
and the same emission by scope so you
can see emission by scope for carbon
emission scope three so emission to
scope two emission scope
one and CO2 analyzis CO2 equivalent
analyzis so this is carbon equalent
analysis this is calculated from all
your emissions when you uh transfer all
to carbon equivalent this is carbon
equivalent emission by category carbon
credit by month because carbon credit is
important if you are purchasing carbon
credit so you can measure how many
credits you bought by per month and this
one is really good to compare your
emissions versus your Revenue so this is
important because it can show an impact
if you are increasing your uh carbon
emissions directly with a growth of
Revenue or you are saving so it can it
can give you some additional uh valuable
information about your emissions and as
I mentioned we have social analyzis so
you can find again the most important
kpis about male and female employees
other employees so you you can track all
of them through akis absense hars uh
then
amount uh gender distribution age
distribution inactive employees
terminated employees then employee
qualifications and employee in unions
currently there is not so much
information on employees so this is what
we created in this moment for social
analysis but we are planning to expand
this uh this report in the
future and what is important this is uh
set of reports we are covering in this
moment but as new features are coming
every way related to sustainability we
are trying to improve powerbi reporting
related to this functionality if you
remember when we started we had only
three reports three extra reports but
now we will enrich reporting
functionality with a many many good and
nice powerbi
reports so before I close this session I
would like to invite you to watch
another uh sustainability sessions
because in this way we deliver so many
different sustainability features and we
have eight different sessions related to
sustainability in this busy Central
lunch event so thank you for watching
this video